Mikhail Salnikov

Mikhail Salnikov

+79271723059

zlat1997@gmail.com

https://github.com/MihailSalnikov

http://deepdivision.net/

Professional Profile

A highly organised data scientist with experience in web programming and cyber security with over 2 years experience. Bachelor of applied mathematics and informatics with good academic record. IT enthusiast with interest to data science and cyber security. Now I study in Skoltech on data science track where I participate in the researches of the <u>ADASE</u> group.

Education

Skolkovo Institute of Science and Technology

Msc. Student in Data Science

2019 - now, Russia, Skolkovo (Moscow)

Mordovian State University

B.S. of Science in Applied Mathematics and Information Technologies

2014 - 2018, Russia, Saransk

Professional Experience

Student / ADASE group

October 2019 -

Academic research in ML and DL.

Wallarm / Data Scientist

March 2018 -

ML and DL research and development in the cyber security area.

Wallarm / Data Scientist intern

February 2017 - March 2018

ML and DL research and development in the cyber security area.

Freelance

2014 - February 2017

Ruby on Rails web development.

_								_		••		
Т	\mathbf{a}	\sim	h	n	1	ca	м	C	v	ı		c
	_						ш.	_	n	ı	. L	

Data Science:

Deep Learning, Machine Learning, Statistics

Tools:

TensorFlow, PyTorch, Scikit Learn, Pandas, NumPy and SciPy, Docker, Spark, Docker, gRPC, MongoDB

Languages:

Python, SQL, Ruby, C/C++, JavaScript

Other:

OWASP TOP 10, ANTLR

Linguistic Skills

English - Intermediate

Russian - Native